Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/long-nguyen-b404b81b5 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microservices
Spring Boot
Java

Long Nguyen

Java Backend Developer Hanoi

Summary

Currently, I work on the backend side of Spring Boot and Nodejs (as a beginner). In addition to that, I am comfortable with frontend technologies (reactjs in particular). I have experience to work with some kind of database like MySqI, MongoDB, Redis, and message queue broker like Kafka and maybe a little bit of Redis pubsub/ stream.

Experience

TTC Solutions
Back End Developer
May 2021 - Present (7 months)
Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

SVMC

Back End Developer June 2018 - May 2021 (3 years)

Education

Hanoi University of Science and Technology
Bachelor's degree, Electrical and Electronics Engineering · (June 2013 - June 2018)

Activity

10/28/2021, Message sent by Nga Lê (Lenka)

11/01/2021, Viewed by Nga Lê (Lenka)